Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 1)
  - Annual Meeting
    - Annual Meeting 1962
      - A Meeting, Economic Conference, Victor Weingarten Publication, 1962-63 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Annual Meeting, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting 1961
      - Men's Committee, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - Professional Staff Meeting, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - Symposium, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - General, Mimeos, etc., 1961 (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - Annual Meeting, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Annual Meeting 1960
      - Dinner Invitations, Correspondence, General, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Lasker Award, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Professional Staff Meeting, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Speaker, General Draper, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Symposium, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Dinner Invitations
        - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 6)
        - Invitations, General, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Annual Meeting, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting 1959
      - Professional Staff Meeting, Evaluation Sheets and Minutes, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Luncheon, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Evaluation, Suggestions, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Membership Meeting, 1959-60 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Symposium, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Staff Session, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - General, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Annual Meeting, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting 1958
      - NYC Hospital Controversy, Workshop Correspondence, 1958-59 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Parliamentarians, 1958-61 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - General, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - General, Mimeos, etc., 1958 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting 1957, Luncheon, Tickets, Invitations, undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Annual Meeting 1956
      - Education for Marriage Seminar, 1955-56 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Re: Panel Discussion on Education for Marriage, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Program, 1955-56 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - 1.61 Administration
    - Alignment Plan, 1964 1964 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Services, 1967-68 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - AID/CWS Program, Administration, Correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Budgets
      - Application of Administration Income to Over-Head Costs, 1977-78 (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - Administration, Correspondence
        - 1973-74 (Box 44, Folder 29)
        - 1975-78 (Box 44)
        - 1970-72 (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - Budget Assumptions, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - Program Budget and Organizational Plan, 1980, Budget and Finance Committee, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - Explanation of Major Budget, Variations, 1980-81 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - Expense Budget Summary by Department and Function, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - Interim Budget and Program Reorganization, 1978-79 (Box 44, Folder 35)
      - Resources' Income and Expense: Projected, Actual, and Budgeted, 1978-79 (Box 44, Folder 36)
      - Revised Budget Proposal, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 37)
      - Proposed Unrestricted Budget, Revisions, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 38)
      - Administration, Activities, Tentative Budget, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 39)
      - Budget Estimates, 1977-78 (Box 44, Folder 40)
      - Legal Services, Budget, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 41)
      - Program Budget Plans, 1977-78 (Box 44, Folder 42)
      - Proposed C/Y Budget, 1977-78 (Box 44, Folder 43)
      - Administration, Unrestricted Income, Unrestricted Expenditures, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Budgets, 1977-78 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Special Restricted Fund Balances as of December 31, 1977, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Activities by Department, CY 1977 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Implementing the Program Budget, Standard Operating Procedures, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Administration, Amended Unrestricted Budget, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Program and Budget Plan: 1977-78 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Strategy to Reduce Projected Deficits, W. Gilbert, Treasurer, 1977-78 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Calendarized Budget, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Expense vs. Budget
        - Analysis, Cumulative from January 1977 (Box 45, Folder 10)
        - Statement, Jan. 1 through April 30, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Administration, Preliminary Report on CY 1977 Program, Activity Outcome, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Resources Department Budget, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Proposed Budget for Calendar Year, 1976-77 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Administration
        - Unrestricted Income, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 15)
        - Proposed Budget for Calendar Year 1977, Program Budget Plans PPFA, 1976-77 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Administration, Budget for Calendar Year 1976, Amended by the Executive Committee, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Calendarized Budget, 1976-77 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Administration, 1976 Short-Term Plan, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Supplemental Budget Requests, 1975-76 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Administration
        - Proposed PPWP Budget for 1975-76 (Box 45, Folder 21)
        - Field Dept. Projected Budget, 1975-76 (Box 45, Folder 22)
        - Budget for Calendar Year 1975, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 23)
        - Comments on Proposed 1975 Budget, Affiliates, Regional, Others, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 24)
        - Plan for 1975, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 25)
        - Proposed PP/WP Budget for 1975, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 26)
        - Budget, 1973-74 (Box 45, Folder 27)
        - Revenues, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 28)
        - Budget, 1972-73 (Box 45, Folder 29)
        - Project Planning for 1973 Budget, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 30)
        - Budget for Fiscal Year 1971-72 (Box 45, Folder 31)
        - Analysis of Deficit, Fiscal Year, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 32)
        - Budget, 1970-71 (Box 45, Folder 33)
        - PPWP Expenditures by Dept., 1970-71 (Box 45, Folder 34)
        - Program Budget, 1970-71 (Box 45, Folder 35)
        - Analysis Field Expenditure, Actual and 1970-71 Budget, 1967-71 (Box 45, Folder 36)
        - Budget, 1969-70 (Box 45, Folder 37)
        - Analysis, Deficit by Department, 1969-70 (Box 45, Folder 38)
        - Proposed Budget, 1969-70 (Box 45, Folder 39)
        - Budget, 1968-69 (Box 45, Folder 40)
        - Program Budget 1968-69 (Box 45, Folder 41)
        - Departmental Budgets: Unrestricted and Restricted, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 42)
        - Detailed Analysis Budgeted vs. Actual Headquarters Expenditures, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 43)
      - Federation Departmental Budget, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 44)
      - Administration, Budget Reductions 1967 (Box 45, Folder 45)
      - Proposed Budget, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 46)
      - Resolutions, Revised Budget and Six Months Budget, Financial Statements, Proposed Headquarters Budget, 1967-68 (Box 45, Folder 47)
      - Revenue of PP Affiliates, 1966-71 (Box 45, Folder 48)
      - Cash Flow to IPPF, 1968-74 (Box 45, Folder 49)
      - Budget, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 50)
    - Notes 1963-65 (Box 45, Folder 51)
    - Planning, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 52)
    - Concurring Organizations, Administration, Correspondence, 1969-73 (Box 45, Folder 53)
    - All Staff Memos
      - Andrews, David, 1978-80 (Box 45, Folder 54)
      - Blaise, Hans, 1975-78 (Box 45, Folder 55)
      - Marshall, Tenny, Senior Staff, 1977-78 (Box 45, Folder 56)
      - Robbins, John C., 1970-74 (Box 45, Folder 57)
      - Vaughn, Jack H., 1975-77 (Box 45, Folder 58)
      - Wattleton, Faye, 1978-80 (Box 45, Folder 59)
      - Miscellaneous Staff
        - 1969-74 (Box 45, Folder 60)
        - 1975-80 (Box 45)
        - 1970-74 (Box 45, Folder 61)
        - 1975-77 (Box 45)
        - Robbins, John C.
          - 1970-74 (Box 45, Folder 62)
          - 1975 (Box 45)
        - 1967-69 (Box 45, Folder 63)
    - Department Head
      - Meetings
        - 1972-74 (Box 45, Folder 64)
        - 1975 (Box 45)
      - Minutes
        - 1972-74 (Box 45, Folder 65)
        - 1975-78 (Box 45)
        - 1960-69 (Box 45, Folder 66-67)
    - Fact Sheet on Present Organizational Practices and Structures, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Federation Income Statistics, 1960-73 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Planned Parenthood Issues Manual: What It Is and How to Use It, circa 1980 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - The Need for a National Headquarters, 1971 (Tsuruoka) (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Newsletter, Mrs. Guttmacher, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Population Dialogue, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Population Steering Committee, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Programs and Objectives
      - 1970 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1969-71 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Closing the Gap, 1966-67 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Recommendations by the Membership, Changes in Priorities, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Establishment of Priorities for Community Attention, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - PPFA-WPEC Program, Alan F. Guttmacher, MD, President, 1963-70 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - A Proposal for a 1971/76 Plan for Planned Parenthood (Staff Paper), Draft, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - A Survey of the PP Movement Here and Abroad, Activities and Expenses, 1970-71 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Headquarters
      - Correspondence
        - 501 Mad., General, 1955, 1962-63 (Box 46, Folder 16)
        - 515 Mad.
          - 1963-74 (Box 46, Folder 17)
          - 1975-77 (Box 46)
        - Rms. 4th, 5th, 9th, 10th Floors and Equipment, 1963-67 (Box 46, Folder 18)
        - 545 Mad., 1969-70 (Box 46, Folder 19)
        - 666 Fifth Ave., 1970-73 (Box 46, Folder 20)
        - 810 Seventh Avenue
          - 1969-74 (Box 46, Folder 21)
          - 1975-79 (Box 46)
      - Lease Copies, Miscellaneous, 1960, 1963-66 (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, 1962-71 (Box 46, Folder 23)
      - Rentals, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 24)
      - Headquarters Relocation
        - Correspondence, Memos, General
          - 1974 (Box 46, Folder 25)
          - 1975-78 (Box 46)
        - of Headquarters, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 26)
        - Questionnaire, Affiliates' Replies, 1977-78 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Introduction to the Planned Parenthood Federation of America
      - 1972-74 (Box 46, Folder 28)
      - 1975-80 (Box 46)
    - Administration, Planned Parenthood's Image, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Organization Charts
      - Table of Organization, Volunteers, 1979-80 (Box 46, Folder 30)
      - Headquarters Staff Support and National Board Committee Structure Chart, 1967-74 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Administration
      - Headquarter Organization Chart, 1972-73 (Box 46, Folder 32-33)
      - Headquarters Organization Chart and Volunteer Organization Chart, 1970-71 (Box 46, Folder 34)
      - Headquarters Organization Chart, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - 1.6 Personnel
    - Affirmative Action
      - Quarterly Report to the Vice President, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 36)
      - Administration, 1975-79 (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - PPFA, 810 Seventh Ave., New York, NY 10019
      - Current AAP and Support Data, 1977-79 (Box 46, Folder 38)
      - Current Year Correspondence (and Progress Reports), 1979 (Box 46, Folder 39)
      - EEO-1 Data, 1976-77 (Box 46, Folder 40)
      - Current Union Contracts, Handbooks (EMPTY) (Box 46, Folder 41)
      - Prior Year Correspondence AAP, SCRR (EMPTY) (Box 46, Folder 42)
      - Current Year SCRRF-EOS Notes, 1977-79 (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Biographical Information
      - 1963-74 (Box 46, Folder 44)
      - 1975-79 (Box 46)
    - Children on Office Premises, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - Employees Salaries Paid by Grants or Foundations, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity
      - 1971-74 (Box 46, Folder 47)
      - 1975 (Box 46)
    - Federal Unemployment Insurance, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 48)
    - Forms
      - 1972-74 (Box 46, Folder 49)
      - 1975-79 (Box 46)
    - Fringe Benefits, 1972-74 (Box 46, Folder 50)
    - Gold, Esther, Correspondence and Memos
      - 1970-74 (Box 46, Folder 51)
      - 1975-79 (Box 46)
    - Guide for Writting Work Descriptions, Glossary of Terms Used, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 52)
    - Holidays
      - 1959-74 (Box 46, Folder 53)
      - 1975-80 (Box 46)
  - 1.61 Insurance
    - Administration
      - Insurance, PP Groups
        - Health, Life, Pension, Legal (Paul), 1978 (Box 46, Folder 54)
        - Health, Life, Pension
          - 1975-78 (Box 46, Folder 55)
          - 1974 (Box 46, Folder 56)
          - 1975 (Box 46)
          - 1973 (Box 46, Folder 57)
          - Correspondence, 1970-72 (Box 46, Folder 58-60)
        - Correspondence, 1968-69 (Box 46, Folder 61)
        - Health, Life, Pension; Peat, Marwick, Mitchell Review, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 62)
        - Correspondence, 1964-68 (Box 46, Folder 63)
        - Health, Life, Pension; Mimeos, Memos, Miscellaneous
          - 1969-74 (Box 47, Folder 1)
          - 1975-79 (Box 47)
        - General, Mimeos, Miscellaneous, 1965-68 (Box 47, Folder 2)
        - Mony, 1975-77 (Box 47, Folder 3)
        - Pension
          - Benefit Guaranty Corporation, 1976-77 (Box 47, Folder 4)
          - Plan, Revised, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 5)
          - Plan, Effective September 30, 1976, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - Health, Life, Pension; Pers. Consultant's Report, 1975-77 (Box 47, Folder 7-8)
        - Summary Annual Report, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 9)
        - T.R. Paul and Company, 1976-78 (Box 47, Folder 10)
        - T. R. Paul and Rothkrug, Correspondence with PP NYC, 1976-77 (Box 47, Folder 11)
        - Pension Trustees, 1969-74 (Box 47, Folder 12)
        - Rothkrug, Paul: Health, Life, Pension
          - 1971-74 (Box 47, Folder 13)
          - 1975-78 (Box 47)
  - Personnel
    - Job Classification Committee
      - 1974 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - 1975-77 (Box 47)
    - Job Classifications and Salary Grades
      - 1972-74 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - 1975-79 (Box 47)
    - Job Descriptions
      - 1970-74 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - 1975-77 (Box 47)
    - Position Description Questionnaire, undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Job Openings, 1979-81 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Minority Staff Members, 1969-72 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - La Guardia Community College Class/Work Program, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - General, 1968-74 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Memos
      - 1977-80 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - 1970-74 (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - 1975-77 (Box 47)
      - Miscellaneous, 1953-69 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - New York State Employment Service, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Performance Evaluation, Employee Appraisals
      - 1974 (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - 1975-79 (Box 47)
    - Personnel Practices
      - 1967-74 (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - 1975-78 (Box 47)
      - Legal (Paul), 1978 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Position Descriptions for Public Affairs and Field Accounting Services, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Robbins, John C., References
      - 1968-74 (Box 47, Folder 30)
      - 1975 (Box 47)
    - Selective Services, 1968-74 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Breakdown of Professional and Non-Professional Staff, 1958-73 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Terminations and Resignations, 1968-69 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Changes in Staff, Additions, Corrections, Promotions, 1968-72 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Employment, (Temp.), 1970-72, [MISSING] (Box 47)
    - Policy on Moving Expenses, Temp. Folder, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Vacations, Leaves, etc.
      - 1964-74 (Box 47, Folder 36)
      - 1975-77 (Box 47)
    - Russ, Diane, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - Salaries
      - 1970-74 (Box 47, Folder 38)
      - 1975-79 (Box 47)
    - Reid-Spears, Romaine
      - Director, Appointment November, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, 1980-81 (Box 47, Folder 40)
    - Staff Exchange PPFA/PPNYC, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - PPWP Staff List
      - 1972-74 (Box 47, Folder 42)
      - 1975-80 (Box 47)
      - 1958-71 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    - Staff Members Handbook, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    - Tuition Refund Plan
      - 1972-74 (Box 47, Folder 45)
      - 1975-80 (Box 47)
    - Personnel Procedures
      - 1968-74 (Box 47, Folder 46)
      - 1975 (Box 47)
    - Staff Meetings, Support Staff and Women, 1971-72 (Box 47, Folder 47)
    - Wald, Bobbi, 1973-74 (Box 47, Folder 48)
    - Vacations, Leave of Absence, Compensatory Time Off, 1970-72 (Box 47, Folder 49)
    - [OUT: The Communicator, SEE BELOW: Staff Personnel Advisory Committee Temporarily Moved to Section with Subject Files] (Box 47)
  - 1.61 The Communicator SPAC
    - Staff Personnel Advisory Committee
      - 1969-74 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - 1975-79 (Box 48)
      - Minutes, The Communicator
        - 1976-81 (Box 48, Folder 2-3)
        - 1971-74 (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - 1975 (Box 48)
      - Members List
        - 1970-74 (Box 48, Folder 5)
        - 1975-79 (Box 48)
      - Reports, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Personnel
    - Time Management Training Program by Brouche H. Read, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Voluntary Wage Guidelines, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Material from Mr. Gaye
    - Medical Department
      - Current Status of Price Agreements for Clinic Services and Supplies, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Draft Copy of Five Year Plan for Medical Department, 1976-80 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Endometrial Aspiration
        - 1972-74 (Box 48, Folder 11)
        - 1975 (Box 48)
      - Foreign Medical Graduates in PPWP Clinics, 1970-71 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - History, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Emergency Medical Care, 1976-77 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Indices of Clinic Function, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Job Description, 1967-74 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Crude Spring Survey, Survey of Medical Services in Affiliate Clinics, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Flagyl, Correspondence, 1976-78 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Laboratory Licensing and Standards, 1967-70 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Maintenance of Patient Records, 1972-73 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - For Mr. Gaye, Oral Contraception, 1960-66 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - Medical Department and Public Policy Task Force, Draft, F. Jaffe, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Malpractice Insurance
        - Medical Judgment
          - 1973-74 (Box 48, Folder 23)
          - 1975 (Box 48, Folder 23)
        - 1955-72 (Box 48, Folder 24-27)
      - Medical Audits
        - Proposal, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 28)
        - Audits, 1978-80 (Box 48, Folder 29)
        - Guidelines for Conducting Internal Medical Audits, Studies in PP Affiliates, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 30)
      - Medical Checklist for Medical Site Visitor, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 31)
      - Patient Care Audit
        - Manual, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 32)
        - Workshop, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Paul, Eve
    - Director of Legal Services
      - Abortion, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 34)
      - Applications Employment, 1978-79 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - Vice President for Legal Affairs, Appointment, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - Director of Legal Services, Appointment, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - Legal Department, Attorneys' Workshop, 1979-80 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - Director of Legal Services, Bellotti v. Baird, 1978-79 (Box 48, Folder 39)
    - V.P. for Legal Affairs, Paul, E., Citizens for a Better Environment v. Village of Schaumburg, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - Director of Legal Services
      - Coalitions, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 41)
      - Coalutti v. Franklin formerly Beal v. Franklin, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 42)
      - Commonweal, 1978-79 (Box 48, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence, 1978-80 (Box 48, Folder 44)
      - The Hatch Act, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 45)
      - Informed Consent Article, 1978-79 (Box 48, Folder 46)
      - Internal Revenue Services, 1978-80 (Box 48, Folder 47)
      - Lawyers' Professional Responsibility Board, 1977-78 (Box 48, Folder 48)
      - Legal Services Budget and Criteria for Utilization of National Legal Services, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 49)
      - Litigation Coordinator, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 50)
    - Vice President for Legal Affairs, Litigation Strategy, 1979-81 (Box 48, Folder 51)
    - Director of Legal Services, McFarland v. Atkins, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 52)
    - Vice President for Legal Affairs, Memos, 1978-81 (Box 48, Folder 53-54)
    - McRae Litigation, 1978-80 (Box 48, Folder 55)
    - Legal, Meeting House Program, T.V., 1979 (Box 48, Folder 56)
    - Director of Legal Services
      - PP of Minnesota v. Minnesota, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 57)
      - Minors, 1978-79 (Box 48, Folder 58)
      - Memo, Service to Minors, 1978-80 (Box 48, Folder 59)
    - Vice President for Legal Affairs
      - Nestle Boycott, 1979-80 (Box 48, Folder 60)
      - Permission to Reprint, 1979-80 (Box 48, Folder 61)
    - Director of Legal Services
      - Proposed Revision of Criminal Code, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 62)
      - Shelter Realty v. Allied Maintenance, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 63)
    - Regulations for Staff Members Holding (or Running for) Public Office, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 64)
    - Reporting Procedures for Affiliates Which Have Elected to Lobby, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 65)
    - Legal Department, Request for "Survival Kit" and Related Legal Papers (Harassment), 1979 (Box 48, Folder 66)
    - Vice President for Legal Affairs, Rights of the Father of a Fetus, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 67)
    - Legal Department, Right to Choose, et al. v. Brendan T. Byrne, et al., 1981 (Box 48, Folder 68)
    - Director of Legal Services
      - Shapp v. Casey, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 69)
      - Unions, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 70)
      - Voter Education, 1978-79 (Box 48, Folder 71)
  - Service Mark
    - Correspondence and Memos
      - 1971-74 (Box 48, Folder 72)
      - 1975 (Box 48)
    - Trademark, Registration of Service Mark
      - 1953-74 (Box 48, Folder 73)
      - 1975 (Box 48)
    - Trademark for PPFA from Old Files, Early History, 1933-54 (Box 48, Folder 74)
  - Corbin, Jill, Claims Coordinator
    - Legal Department
      - Corbin, Jill
        - Claims Coordinator, Appointment, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 75)
        - Memos, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 76)
        - Correspondence and Memos, 1979-80 (Box 48, Folder 77)
    - Legal Affairs, Klassel, Dara, Legal Associate, Appointment, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 78)
  - Administration
    - Andrews, David
      - Correspondence, 1978-81 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Affirmative Action, Notice to Vendors, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Legal, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Memos, 1978-81 (Box 49, Folder 4-5)
      - Report to the Membership, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Re: Group Annuity, Contract AC 4680, The Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Chronological, 1979, Do Not Remove Contents (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Blaise, Hans
      - Invitations, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Affirmative Action, Notice to Vendor, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Appointment as Vice President, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Bulk Purchase
        - Ray Belsky, Consultant, 1976-77 (Box 49, Folder 12)
        - Plan, 1976-77 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 1975-78 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Development of a Uniform Info System, Minutes, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - List of Chrons., 1976 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Location of Federation Headquarters, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Memos, 1975-77 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Management Information System for Affiliates, 1977-78 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Status Report on the Development of a Federation Management Info. System, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Office Relocation and Investment, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - The Role of the VP for Operations, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - PPWP Chronological, 1975-76, Do Not Remove Contents (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Dr. Carrera, Michael A.